tattoospot.com 2006-04-25

# TattooSpot.com Privacy Notice

**Tattoo Spot Privacy Statement**

**TattooSpot.com & it's parent Company Tattoospot.com. (“DWP”) Online Privacy Policy   
(Last updated January 1, 2004)**

DWP has established this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our websites. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users. 

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

This privacy policy covers DWP's treatment of personally identifiable information collected by DWP through a website owned and operated by DWP. 

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that DWP does not own or control, or of persons that DWP does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which DWP's websites link.   
**  
Collection and Use of Personal Information**

You can visit the websites of DWP without revealing any personal information. However, DWP needs certain personal information if you wish to purchase our products, register for an affiliate account, receive DWP's newsletter, or use certain DWP services. 

Where required, this information may include your personal contact information and/or your company contact information. DWP will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your member’s account, and to contact you regarding new products and services. 

By accessing the services of DWP and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. 

**Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**

DWP automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. DWP may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, DWP does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you. 

DWP also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and DWP assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage.   
**  
Information Sharing and Disclosure**

DWP may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on behalf of DWP to provide products and services requested by you. We will share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information 

**DWP may otherwise disclose your personal information when:**

a) We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose; 

b) We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process; 

c) We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of DWP; 

d) We find that your actions on our websites violate the DWP Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

**Consent**  
If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to DWP. If you have provided personal information to DWP and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify DWP at webmaster@tattoospot.com. 

**Security**  
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your DWP Information is protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, DWP may use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures. 

Further, DWP retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes identified above or as required by law. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

DWP may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. When it does, DWP will also revise the “last update” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of DWP websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof. 

**Questions or Suggestions**  
If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at webmaster@tattoospot.com.
